loumalnatis.com 2012-12-27

# Lou Malnati's Pizzeria - Privacy Policy

**

We collect information about our users in two different ways, implicitly and explicitly. We learn about our visitors implicitly through the use of log files from our web site and eCommerce sites. Additionally, we collect personal information in order to fulfill users' requests for additional information on our product line, and in the course of taking orders through our eCommerce sites.

When ordering from us in person, over the phone, or through our online ordering eCommerce site, we may ask you to provide your full name, telephone number, email address, delivery address, billing address, and credit card information.

Our eCommerce site records customer information and behavior both at the individual level and in aggregate to help us continually improve our site and provide a better customer experience. In addition, our online ordering eCommerce website uses cookies to store information during the ordering process.

How we use this information

Lou Malnati’s respects our customers' privacy and does not sell any sort of customer information. 

Information gathered by our online ordering eCommerce site is used to prepare your order. 

The information logged by our web site and e-commerce shopping cart is for the purpose of refining the content on our site to provide an enhanced user experience.

The forms on our site give visitors the opportunity to request more information about our product line. User information is used by internal departments to fulfill the request. Customers or visitors may be contacted by Lou Malnati’s as a follow up to their request, question, or comment.

Cookies

We do employ a cookie on our site for use by our online ordering eCommerce site. (A cookie is a piece of data sent to your browser from a web server and stored on your hard drive). To avoid having a cookie attached, set your browser to refuse all cookies. If you refuse cookies our online ordering eCommerce site will not be available to you.

With whom we share this information

We employ other companies in the course of providing customers with services and products that can be ordered through our web site. Examples include  fulfilling orders, sending postal mail and email, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, processing credit card payments. These companies or individuals have access to personal information needed to perform their functions, but may not use it for other purposes.

The Lou Malnati’s site may contain links to other sites. Please remember that the privacy practices these sites uphold may differ from ours. 

If you have any questions about this privacy statement or how we handle our customers' personal information, please feel free to call our corporate office at 847-562-1814 or fill out the contact form [here](http://www.loumalnatis.com/About/contact.aspx) to send us an email.

Changes to our privacy policy

Lou Malnati’s reserves the right to change the privacy policy without notice to the individual or visitor.

Effective date of the policy

Lou Malnati’s Privacy Policy was last updated and became effective on February 13th, 2012.

**
